A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1992-1993
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1992-1993
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.961
This colleciton consists of 30,500 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred on 1996 February 13.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by John Thomas Casteen, the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
The papers consist of: general and committee files.
Organization
SERIES I: General Files, 1992-1993 Boxes 1-56
SERIES II: Committee Files, 1992-1993 Boxes 57-60
SERIES III: Restricted Files, 1992-1993 Box 61
Contents List
- SERIES I: General Files
  - "A-Al" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - "Am-Az" Miscellaneous (1-3 of 5) 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - "Am-Az" Miscellaneous (4-5 of 5) 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - Admissions/Alumni--Medical School 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - African-American Affairs (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - African-American Affairs--Woodson Institute 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - Admissions--Law School--(Restricted) 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - Admissions--General (4 folders) (Restricted) 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association--General and Board of Managers (1-3 of 5) 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association--General and Board of Managers (4-5 of 5) 1992-1993 (Box 3)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities 1992-1993 (Box 3)
  - American Council on Education (3 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 3)
  - Annual Reports--President's Reports 1992-1993 (Box 3)
  - Anthropology--General 1992-1993 (Box 3)
  - Applications for Positions "A-Z" (4 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 4)
  - Architecture--General 1992-1993 (Box 4)
  - Art--General 1992-1993 (Box 4)
  - Art--Bayly Art Museum 1992-1993 (Box 4)
  - Asian Studies 1992-1993 (Box 4)
  - Associated Chief Admissions Officers of Public Universities 1992-1993 (Box 5)
  - Associated Western Universities 1992-1993 (Box 5)
  - Association of American Colleges 1992-1993 (Box 5)
  - Association of American Universities (3 folders) 1992-1993 Jan-Jun (Box 5)
  - Association of American Universities (4 folders) 1992-1993 Jun-Dec (Box 6)
  - Association of Governing Boards (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 7)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges and Universities 1992-1993 (Box 7)
  - Astronomy--General 1992-1993 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--General (1-3 of 6) 1992-1993 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--General (4-6 of 6) 1992-1993 (Box 8)
  - Athletics--Atlantic Coast Conference (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 8)
  - Athletics--College Football Association 1992-1993 (Box 9)
  - Athletics--National Collegiate Athletic Association (3 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 9)
  - Athletics--National Collegiate Athletic Association--(Restricted) 1992-1993 (Box 9)
  - Attorney General--State 1992-1993 (Box 9)
  - Auditor--Internal--General (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 10)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts 1992-1993 (Box 10)
  - "Ba-Bm" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 10)
  - "Bn-Br" Miscellaneous (1 of 2) 1992-1993 (Box 10)
  - "Bn-Br" Miscellaneous (2 of 2) 1992-1993 (Box 11)
  - "Bs-Bz" Miscellaneous 1992-1993 (Box 11)
  - Biology--General 1992-1993 (Box 11)
  - Birdwood--General 1992-1993 (Box 11)
  - Business and Finance--General (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 11)
  - Business and Finance--General--Updates (1of 2) 1992-1993 (Box 11)
  - Business and Finance--General--Updates (2 of 2) 1992-1993 (Box 12)
  - "Ca-Cg" Miscellaneous (5 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 12)
  - "Ch-Cn" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 13)
  - "Co-Cz" Miscellaneous (1-2 of 5) 1992-1993 (Box 13)
  - "Co-Cz" Miscellaneous (3-5 of 5) 1992-1993 (Box 14)
  - Career Planning and Placement 1992-1993 (Box 14)
  - Casteen--General (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 15)
  - Casteen--General--(Restricted) 1992-1993 (Box 15)
  - Casteen--Class (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 15)
  - Cavalier Daily 1992-1993 (Box 15)
  - Center for Innovative Technology (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 15)
  - Center for Public Service 1992-1993 (Box 16)
  - Charlottesville, City of 1992-1993 (Box 16)
  - Charlottesville Planning and Coordination Council 1992-1993 (Box 16)
  - Classics 1992-1993 (Box 16)
  - Chemistry--General 1992-1993 (Box 16)
  - Clinch Valley College--General (3 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 16)
  - College of Arts and Sciences 1992-1993 (Box 17)
  - The College Board--General (3 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 17)
  - College Board--CAPS (1 of 2) 1992-1993 (Box 17)
  - College Board--CAPS (2 of 2) 1992-1993 (Box 18)
  - College Board Annual Retreat 1992-1993 (Box 18)
  - Commerce--General 1992-1993 (Box 18)
  - Comptroller--State 1992-1993 (Box 18)
  - Condolences "A-Z" (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 18)
  - Congress--General 1992-1993 (Box 19)
  - Consortia--Central Virginia 1992-1993 (Box 19)
  - Consortia--Tidewater 1992-1993 (Box 19)
  - Continuing Education (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 19)
  - "Da-De" Miscellaneous 1992-1993 (Box 19)
  - "Df-Dz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 19)
  - Council of Presidents (State) 1992-1993 (Box 20)
  - Darden School of Business (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 20)
  - Dean's Meetings 1992-1993 (Box 20)
  - Development--General (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 20)
  - Development--General (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 21)
  - Drama--General 1992-1993 (Box 21)
  - "E" Miscellaneous ( 3 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 21)
  - Education--General 1992-1993 (Box 22)
  - Engineering and Applied Science--General (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 22)
  - Educational Testing Service (ETS) 1992-1993 (Box 22)
  - Enrollment--General 1992-1993 (Box 22)
  - English--General (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 22)
  - Department of English--(Restricted) 1992-1993 (Box 22)
  - Enrollment Statistics 1992-1993 (Box 23)
  - Enrollment--Growth Report (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 23)
  - Environmental Science--General 1992-1993 (Box 23)
  - Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 23)
  - Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action--(Restricted) 1992-1993 (Box 24)
  - "Fa-Fh" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 24)
  - "Fi-Fr" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 24)
  - Facilities Management 1992-1993 (Box 24)
  - Faculty--General 1992-1993 (Box 25)
  - Faculty--Letters 1992-1993 (Box 25)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences 1992-1993 (Box 25)
  - Family Violence Prevention Fund 1992-1993 (Box 25)
  - Financial Aid to Students 1992-1993 (Box 25)
  - Food Services (Dining Services) 1992-1993 (Box 25)
  - "Ga-Gn" Miscellaneous (1-2 of 3) 1992-1993 (Box 25)
  - "Ga-Gn" Miscellaneous (3 of 3) 1992-1993 (Box 26)
  - "Go-Gz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 26)
  - General Assembly--General (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 26)
  - General Assembly--Legislative Summaries 1992-1993 (Box 26)
  - General Assembly--House Appropriations 1992-1993 (Box 27)
  - General Assembly--Senate Finance 1992-1993 (Box 27)
  - General Council--General 1992-1993 (Box 27)
  - General Services--State 1992-1993 (Box 27)
  - German Language and Literature 1992-1993 (Box 27)
  - Gifts and Grants "A-C" (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 27)
  - Gifts and Grants "D-F" 1992-1993 (Box 27)
  - Gifts and Grants "G-K" 1992-1993 (Box 27)
  - Gifts and Grants "L-P" (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 28)
  - Gifts and Grants "Q-S" (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 28)
  - Gifts and Grants"T-Z" 1992-1993 (Box 28)
  - Governor's Inauguration 1992-1993 (Box 28)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs 1992-1993 (Box 29)
  - Governmental Relations 1992-1993 (Box 29)
  - Governor's Office--General (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 29)
  - Governor's Office--Administration 1992-1993 (Box 29)
  - Governor's Office--Economic Development 1992-1993 (Box 29)
  - Governor's Office--Education 1992-1993 (Box 29)
  - Governor's Office--Finance 1992-1993 (Box 29)
  - Governor's Office--Health and Human Resources 1992-1993 (Box 30)
  - Governor's Office--Natural Resources and Public Safety 1992-1993 (Box 30)
  - Governor's Office--Washington Liaison Office 1992-1993 (Box 30)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1992-1993 (Box 30)
  - "Ha-Hn" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 30)
  - "Hi-Hz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 30)
  - Harrison Foundation 1992-1993 (Box 31)
  - History--General 1992-1993 (Box 31)
  - Honor System 1992-1993 (Box 31)
  - Human Resources 1992-1993 (Box 31)
  - Human Resources--Key Advantage Program 1992-1993 (Box 31)
  - "I" Miscellaneous (1 of 2) 1992-1993 (Box 31)
  - "I" Miscellaneous (2 of 2) 1992-1993 (Box 32)
  - Information Technology--State 1992-1993 (Box 32)
  - Information Technology--University 1992-1993 (Box 32)
  - International Students 1992-1993 (Box 32)
  - International Studies 1992-1993 (Box 32)
  - "J" Miscellaneous (1-2 of 3) 1992-1993 (Box 32)
  - "J" Miscellaneous (3 of 3) 1992-1993 (Box 33)
  - Jefferson Memorial Foundation 1992-1993 (Box 33)
  - Jefferson Scholars 1992-1993 (Box 33)
  - Jeffersonian Restoration Board (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 33)
  - Jeffersonian Restoration and Advisory Board Dinner 1992-1993 (Box 33)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Committee 1992-1993 (Box 33)
  - "K" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 34)
  - "L" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 34)
  - Law School--General (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 34)
  - Lawn Use Policy 1992-1993 (Box 35)
  - Library--General (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 35)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous 1992-1993 (Box 35)
  - "Ma-Me" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 35)
  - "Mf-Mz" Miscellaneous (1 of 2) 1992-1993 (Box 35)
  - "Mf-Mz" Miscellaneous (2 of 2) 1992-1993 (Box 36)
  - Major Events, Office Of 1992-1993 (Box 36)
  - Marine Science 1992-1993 (Box 36)
  - Mariners Museum (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 36)
  - Materials Management--Purchasing 1992-1993 (Box 36)
  - Mathematics--General 1992-1993 (Box 36)
  - Medical Center--General (1 of 5) 1992-1993 (Box 36)
  - Medical Center (2-5 of 5) 1992-1993 (Box 37)
  - Medical Center--Health Sciences Council 1992-1993 (Box 37)
  - Medical Center--Hospital 1992-1993 (Box 37)
  - Medical Center--Medical School 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Medical Center--Nursing 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Medical Center--Personnel 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Music--General 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - "N-Na" Miscellaneous (1-2 of 5) 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - "N-Na" Miscellaneous (3-5 of 5) 1992-1993 (Box 39)
  - "Nb-Nz" Miscellaneous (1-2 of 3) 1992-1993 (Box 39)
  - "Nb-Nz" Miscellaneous (3 of 3) 1992-1993 (Box 40)
  - NASULGC--General (3 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 40)
  - NASULGC--Board on Oceans and Atmosphere (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 41)
  - NASULGC--Committee on International Exchange 1992-1993 (Box 41)
  - NASULGC--Green Circulars 1992-1993 (Box 41)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF) 1992-1993 (Box 41)
  - Newcomb Hall 1992-1993 (Box 41)
  - New England Education Loan Marketing (NELLIE MAE) (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 41)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa Foundation, Incorporated 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - "Pa-Ph" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - "Pi-Pz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 43)
  - Parking and Transportation (State) 1992-1993 (Box 43)
  - Parking--General 1992-1993 (Box 43)
  - Personnel--General 1992-1993 (Box 43)
  - Personnel and Training--State 1992-1993 (Box 43)
  - Philosophy--General 1992-1993 (Box 43)
  - Psychology 1992-1993 (Box 44)
  - Physics 1992-1993 (Box 44)
  - Planning, Assessment and Studies 1992-1993 (Box 44)
  - Planning and Budget--State (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 44)
  - Planning and Budget--University of Virginia 1992-1993 (Box 44)
  - President's Senior Cabinet Meetings 1992-1993 (Box 44)
  - Promotions and Tenure--General 1992-1993 (Box 44)
  - Provost--general 1992-1993 (Box 44)
  - Associate Provost for Research 1992-1993 (Box 45)
  - QATAR--Gulf Cooperation Council 1992-1993 (Box 45)
  - "Ra-Rh" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 45)
  - "Ri-Rz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 45)
  - Real Estate Foundation (UREF) 1992-1993 (Box 45)
  - Recommendations "A-Z" (3 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 46)
  - Registrar 1992-1993 (Box 46)
  - Religious Studies 1992-1993 (Box 46)
  - ROTC--General 1992-1993 (Box 46)
  - ROTC--Air Force 1992-1993 (Box 46)
  - ROTC--Army 1992-1993 (Box 46)
  - ROTC--Navy 1992-1993 (Box 46)
  - Salaries-(Restricted) 1992-1993 (Box 46)
  - "Sa-Sn" Miscellaneous (1 of 3) 1992-1993 (Box 46)
  - "Sa-Sn" Miscellaneous (2-3 of 3) 1992-1993 (Box 47)
  - "So-Sz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 47)
  - Sponsored Programs Office 1992-1993 (Box 48)
  - SCHEV (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 48)
  - SCHEV--General Assembly (1-3 of 5) 1992-1993 (Box 48)
  - SCHEV--General Assembly (4-5 of 5) 1992-1993 (Box 49)
  - SCHEV--Commission on the University of the 21st Century 1992-1993 (Box 49)
  - SCHEV--Notes 1992-1993 (Box 49)
  - SCHEV--Research Note 1992-1993 (Box 49)
  - SCHEV-- Campus Climate 1992-1993 (Box 49)
  - Senate (University) Faculty (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 49)
  - Sociology 1992-1993 (Box 50)
  - State Department of Education 1992-1993 (Box 50)
  - Student Affairs--General 1992-1993 (Box 50)
  - LILKY/SACS (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 50)
  - Student Affairs--General 1992-1993 (Box 51)
  - Student Affairs--Fraternities and Sororities 1992-1993 (Box 51)
  - Student Council 1992-1993 (Box 51)
  - Student Council--Minutes 1992-1993 (Box 51)
  - "Ta-Te" Miscellaneous ( 2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 51)
  - "Te-Tz" Miscellaneous ( 1 of 2) 1992-1993 (Box 51)
  - "Te-Tz" Miscellaneous (2 of 2) 1992-1993 (Box 52)
  - "U" Miscellaneous ( 4 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 52)
  - United Way--Combined Charity Campaign 1992-1993 (Box 53)
  - University Research Association, Inc. 1992-1993 (Box 53)
  - University Guides 1992-1993 (Box 53)
  - University Journal 1992-1993 (Box 53)
  - University Police 1992-1993 (Box 53)
  - University Press Of Virginia 1992-1993 (Box 53)
  - University Relations--News Office (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 53)
  - University Union 1992-1993 (Box 53)
  - "V" Miscellaneous (1-2 of 5) 1992-1993 (Box 53)
  - "V" Miscellaneous (3-5 of 5) 1992-1993 (Box 54)
  - Virginia Festival of American Film (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 54)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1992-1993 (Box 54)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1992-1993 (Box 54)
  - "Wa-Wh"Miscellaneous ( 3 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 55)
  - "Wi-Wz" Miscellaneous (1-3 of 4) 1992-1993 (Box 55)
  - "Wi-Wz" Miscellaneous (4 of 4) 1992-1993 (Box 56)
  - "X, Y, Z" Miscellaneous 1992-1993 (Box 56)
- SERIES II: Committee Files
  - Admissions 1992-1993 (Box 57)
  - Arboretum and Landscape 1992-1993 (Box 57)
  - Athletics Advisory Council 192-1993 (Box 57)
  - Calender 1992-1993 (Box 57)
  - Commencement and Convocations 1992-1993 (Box 57)
  - Dining Services/Residential life 1992-1993 (Box 57)
  - Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action 1992-1993 (Box 57)
  - Faculty Benefits 1992-1993 (Box 57)
  - Financial Aid 1992-1993 (Box 57)
  - Founders Day 1992-1993 (Box 57)
  - General 1992-1993 (Box 57)
  - Housing 1992-1993 (Box 57)
  - Information Technology/Communications 1992-1993 (Box 57)
  - Interests of Persons with Disabilities 1992-1993 (Box 57)
  - International Students 1992-1993 (Box 57)
  - Judiciary (4 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 58)
  - Libraries 1992-1993 (Box 58)
  - Master Planning Council 1992-1993 (Box 58)
  - Names 1992-1993 (Box 58)
  - Proxy Advisory 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Radiation Safety 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Residential Life 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Rhodes Scholarship 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Safety and Security 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Scheduling 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Security 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Sexual Assault/Judiciary Policy (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Thomas Jefferson Award 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Traffic Appeals 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Transportation and Parking 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - University Press of Virginia 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - University Research Policy Advisory 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Vice President 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Virginia Status of University Students 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Virginia Status of University Students--(Restricted) 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Women's Concerns (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 60)
- SERIES III: Restricted Files (Box 61)